嫌です
書き直せ
「夢」 市ノ宮行
帰りの車の中で父さんは言った
俺は珍しく平凡な作文を書いた
あの作文 探せば まだあるかな
宿題に出ていた作文 「将来の夢」
そんな漠然とした目標では
なにも できはしない
私がどんな人間なのか
お前に分かるはずもない
昔 一度だけ授業参観日に父さんが来た
僕は将来 お父さんのような
強い人になりたいと思っています
今になって思うと… あの日
俺は夢を語りたかったわけでなく
目覚めのキッスはまどろむあなたに
あやかしリップなお姫様
だからこそ父に恐らく最初で最後であろう
小さな反抗もしたんだろう
It was the only time Father ever
came to Parents' Day.
出会いの切符は夢見るあなたに
まやかし VIP なエア・フォース
"My Dream," by Ichinomiya Ko.
Dreams
Ko
would like to be
like my father
時間がないの いま何時？
授業開始の５分前
I wish to become a powerful man, like my father.
急いでないの いま大事
あなたに出会う５分前
It was an essay on my goals for the future.
The topic was pretty run-of-the-mill.
I ask you to lend me your great strength for just a little longer!
When we've succeeded, I will then be able to join my father, Zeon!
ヴィーナスお隣さんなの どうして？
知らない間に
I ask you to lend me your great strength for just a little longer!
When we've succeeded, I will then be able to join my father, Zeon!
Essay
ジーザスお向かいさんなの
聞いてやばいの
Essay
On the car ride home, Father said to me:
You couldn't possibly understand
what kind of man I am.
大胆あいつの攻撃
バイバイ気づいてない振り
大胆あいつの衝撃 まさに生き地獄
You'll never accomplish anything
with such a vague goal.
寝起きのキックは挨拶代わりに
生足いっつも傷だらけ
Rewrite it.
Thinking about it now,
my true purpose that day wasn't
simply to discuss my dreams.
手持ちのチップをあの子に賭けたら
まばたきみっつでノック・ダウン
Daddy!
嫌いじゃないの 嫌なだけ
予測出来ないこの気持ち
期待しないで 暇なだけ
あなたと消える５分間
No.
That's probably why...
ヴィーナスあの子はいつでもそうなの？
いまなら間に合う
I talked back to him for the
first time. And the last.
ジーザス引き返せないの 早く気付いて
I wonder if that essay's still
laying around somewhere.
Chapter 62: "Lies"
Two shadows creep into Rec's room.
いつものリクの部屋に
見慣れない人影が２つ
They are employees from Rec's top company.
彼らはリクが外で経営する会社の社員
Secretary Takai,
秘書の高井と
and his assistant, Shimazaki.
その助手の島崎であった
Master Ko, when I spotted you from
up on the bridge the other day,
行様 先日 橋の上からお見かけした時は
何事かと思いましたが…
I didn't understand what I was seeing.
I had no idea you were living like this.
まさか そんな事情がおありだったとは
Why didn't you come to us about this earlier?
なぜもっと早く
打ち明けて下さらなかったのです！
Please, we're here for you.
Let us help you with this!
わたくし達にも
どうか手伝わせください！ その…
Let us help develop your plan to build a
power generator using the Arakawa River!
荒川を利用した原発をも凌ぐ
発電ビジネスというものを！
Rec tells his secretaries one whopper of a story.
リクは秘書たちに大嘘をついていた
So...
で… 本当に起業してたと思わせるために
部下のふりをしろってわけなのね
You want us to act like your employees to make
it look like you're here on business. Right?
Yup. And amazingly, you all look quite normal.
ええ あなた方なら
ビジュアルはまともですからね
Sort of.
ふっ にしても 橋の下に会社を作っているなど
随分 無茶な嘘をついたものだ
Regardless, the idea that you need to lie
about creating a business down here...
It's kind of ridiculous, don't you think?
Maybe, but I can't let them find out the
real reason for me being down here.
それでも ここにいる本当の理由を
知られるわけにはいかないんです
でも珍しいねえ きみが頼みごとなんて
Still... I'm surprised you'd ask
for a favor in the first place.
Of course I don't expect you to do it for free.
もちろんタダでとは言いませんよ
Keep those nice designer suits I
bought for you, and we'll call it even.
その最上級のスーツで
貸し借りなしですからねえ
Oh my goodness, Rec.
あらあらリク君 こんなスーツ１着で
私が言うことを聞くと思ってるの？
You really think these clothes are
enough to make me submit to you?
You've got a lot of nerve. Did you
honestly believe I'd agree to that?
まははっ 図々しい
当然引き受けてくれるとでも
思ったのかしら？
ドルガバですよ！
上下で300万円ですよお！
Of course I did! Your outfits cost
like 3 million yen all together!
I don't care how expensive they were.
They're simply not worth it.
そんな いくらのスーツだろうが
割に合わないわよ
I mean, think about it. I have
to pretend to be beneath you.
なんせ“あなたより下の立場”なんて
想像を絶するような役を演じるわけだし？
Carnivores
Me
Herbivores
Carnivores
Plants
Microbes
Recruit
Can you possibly imagine anything
on Earth more degrading than that?
Allow me to show you the
proper way to beg for our help.
それ相応の頼み方ってのを
教えてあげるわ
He's late.
遅いですわね 社長
Hrm.
うーん… 待っておれん 少し見てこよう
We can't wait any longer.
Let's go take a look outside.
I've always been amazed at
his most unique business sense.
しかし先日来た時はこんな所で起業を…
と驚いたが それ以上に驚くべきは
But what amazes me even more
is Master Ko's charismatic ability to gather
people from all walks of life under his banner.
どんな場所でも人が集まってくるという
行様のカリスマだな
Prosperity
やはり あの方は人の上に立つ…
Indeed, he was most certainly
born to be on top—
I already told you once, do it right!
そうじゃなーいって言ってるでしょ！
Get your face right into the dirt!
もっと土に頭をつけて！
ミミズになりたいって言いなさい！
Now tell me you want to be an earthworm.
ミ… ミミズに…
I... I want to be—
Master Ko?
行様？
ふ… 今… こいつらに…
契約の取り方を教えていたところでね
I was just... showing them some of
my surefire negotiation tactics!
Boy, talk about intense training.
ちょっといい汗かきました
Chapter 63: "Employees Under the Bridge"
I thought I told you to wait for me.
待っていろと言ったはずなんだが…
申し訳ありません ところで…
こちらがスタッフの方ですかな？
My deepest apologies.
Now then...
Are these your new staff members?
Oh, yes, this is Maria—
ああっ 彼女はマリアといって
Come on, please just play along!
頼む！ 合わせてくれ…！
まあー！ 本当にいいスーツねえ！
Oh my, what an amazing ensemble!
マリアさん！
Maria!
よく似合っているわあ
いいセンスじゃない
That looks great on you.
You have truly superb taste.
お そうですかな？ あ いいやあ
実はあたくしもスーツには…
You think so? I'm actually quite
particular when it comes to—
ちょっと 鏡は動かないでちょうだい
Hey. Hold that mirror perfectly still, would you?
Mirror?
かが…
Next! Next staff member!
次！ 次のスタッフ出て！
初めまして フランツです
Pleased to meet you. I'm Franz.
おお 外国の方ですかな？
Oh, are you perhaps from another country?
Thank God. At least Sister's acting normal.
よかった…
シスターはちゃんとしてくれそうだ
彼は語学が達者でね
６カ国語を話せるんだ
He's a very skilled linguist and translator.
He speaks six different languages.
Wow.
ほお… おおっといけない
名刺をお渡ししなくては…
Ah, where are my manners?
Let me give you my business card.
I'm—
わたくし…
What the hell do you think you're doing?
貴様！ 何のつもりだ！
What do you think you're doing?!
おまえこそ何のつもりだー！
Just put that lighter away, would you?
いいから早く
そんな物騒なライターはしまって！
Oh, it's a lighter?
ああ ライターでしたか
ちっ 何だ紙か
What's this? Paper?
Obviously!
当たり前です！
So then, what other kinds of major projects
have you been involved with in the past?
それでは 今まで手がけた
プロジェクトで代表的なものは？
Dammit, stop making things so difficult!
高井め 面倒な質問を！
Major projects? It's hard to say.
There have been so many...
代表的… さあ なにぶん数が多くて
Dang, that was a nice dodge.
上手いことかわしてくれたな…
Besides...
それに… 戦争はどれも同じ
War... War never changes.
War?
戦…
きみは もう下がっていい！
You can step back now!
They all seem to have very unique personalities.
随分と個性的な方々ですな
ははは 今は個性の時代だからね！
Unique is in these days, you know!
Crap... he's starting to get suspicious.
まずい… 納得してもらえそうな
雰囲気じゃないぞ
Master Ko? Who is that other man over there?
行様… そこにいる あともう１人の方は？
That's right.
そうだ まだシロさんが！
I still have Whitey!
You mean me?
私ですか？
いや！ やっぱりいい 来るなっ！
Never mind! Stay back!
Why do you say that, Master Ko?
なぜですか行様
He seems like a decent and modest man.
腰の低いよさそうな方ではありませんか
ご紹介して下さい
Please introduce us.
No, really, it's okay!
いいんだ彼は本当に！
I can't cover up any more weirdness!
もうこれ以上のフォローは無理！
これでさらにシロさんが白線渡りやら
白色コーニッシュやら言い出したら…
If Whitey starts talking about his
lines and that damn White Cornish...
Sir...
社長
I mean it, stay away!
いいから きみは下がっててくれ！
I see. Please excuse my obtrusiveness, sir.
はっ 出すぎた真似を致しました
ふんん…！
もし彼が不満ならば
本社に回して頂けませんか
Say, if you're discontent with him,
why not send him up to the main office?
マジでえ？
Are you serious?
Whitey—I mean, Shirai Toru—was once
an executive at a major corporation.
シロさん（本名 白井通）は
元大手企業の営業マンでした
Chapter 64: "Secretary"
うん 君のような人がいれば安心ですな
Yes, a man like him would
be great to have around.
Oh no, you're too kind.
いえいえ そんな
Ah, I feel like I'm right back in my old office.
ああ… あそこだけ背景に
オフィスが見えるようだ
Thanks, Whitey.
ありがとう シロさん
So are we all finished here?
じゃあ もう新会社の話はいいかな？
If so, let's head elsewhere and
talk about the main office.
今度は場所を移動して
３人で本社の話でも…
Hey, what are you guys up to?
おい みんなー！ 何やってんだー？
Looks like fun!
楽しそうだな
For real!
ほーんと！
We wanna play too.
仲間に入れて
Just the people I didn't want to see today.
絶対に会わせたくなかった人達来た！
Of course I'd be honored to meet them, as well.
ぜひ ご紹介に預かりたいものですね…
Hey, who's the chrome-dome?
I'm the Village Chie—
よお 何だこのハゲ？ 俺はここの村…
Boy, isn't he just adorable?
いやあ 本当可愛いなあ
He's our official mascot, Kappatsukun.
これは うちのマスコットキャラクター
かっぱつ君だ
Ah, so that explains the costume—
ああ だから彼は着ぐるみを
The hell you say? I'm not wearing anyth—
何だと 俺は何１つ着てなんて
Kids today love that whole
"rude punk" thing, ya know?
口が悪いのが斬新だろ？
And this young lady here?
そちらのお嬢さんは？
Oh, this is Nino—
ああ 彼女はニノさ… い！
ニノ… ニイノ 新野さん…
Nino... Niino... Miss Niino!
Yeah! Miss Niino, my secretary.
そう新野さん 秘書だ！
Secretary?
秘書？
You mean, like myself?
あたくしと同じですか…
Just play along, okay?
ってことにして下さいね
So... Miss Niino, is it?
新野さんと仰ったか…
As a veteran secretary, I must tell you this.
老婆心ながら言わせて頂きたい
This position is both solemn and crucial.
秘書というのは とても重要かつ
厳しい職務だということを
You must have enduring strength, a sense of
responsibility, and a compassionate heart.
責任感と忍耐力 気配り
For example, I'm determined to devote
myself, mind and body, to Master Ko!
そして何より あるじたる行様に
身も心も捧げる覚悟！
新野様！ あなたにそれが おあ…
Miss Niino, do you feel you are equipped—
The best women... are those women...
With the one-length hair!
女性はぁワンレンが一番だぁよー
じゃあ私も星君のために
ワンレンにしようかしら？
Maybe I should get a haircut.
You know, for Hoshi.
Are you paying attention?!
聞いておりますのか！
あっ すまない高井！ 何？
Sorry, Takai! What'd you say?
What happened?
どうした？
I'm asking you if you're prepared to
pledge your undying loyalty to Master Ko!
行様に忠義を誓う覚悟があるかと
聞いておるのです！
Definitely not.
そんなものはない
How can you say that?!
なんと！ 行様 なぜこのような者を！
Master Ko, why on Earth would
you choose this woman?
Nino, I'm really sorry, but can't
you just pretend for now?
二ッ ニノさん すみませんけど
今だけ秘書ってことに
嫌だ！
No way!
ニノさん！
Nino!
No matter what, I'm always gonna be your lover!
私はいつだってお前の恋人でいるんだ！
Lover?
恋人…？
Um, I'm glad to hear that, but for right now—
あの！ 嬉しいですが今は…
嫌だ！
No!
まあまあ社長 高井さんだって
社長に恋人がいることくらい許してくれ…
Now, now, sir. I'm sure Mr. Takai would
happily approve of you having a girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
恋人…？
あ 高井さん…？
Mr. Takai?
Girlfriend? So is she...
恋人…
それはあ はっ わたくしよりも
大切なものなのですかあああー！
someone you love more than me?!
This is all a big misunderstanding,
Takai! It's just that...
違うんだ高井 これは何というか…
You haven't been coming in to
the main office lately, either!
だって最近 本社にも帰ってこないし…
I'M SO JEALOOOUUUS!
悔しいいー！
Huh? What the hell?
え？ 何々？
Even the Arakawa residents were freaked out.
さすがの住人もドン引きでした
NOOOOOOO!
Chapter 65: "A Deep Relationship"
窓辺に仲よく寄り添う２つの歯ブラシ
Ah, that smells nice. Is it Earl Grey today?
いい香り… 今日はアールグレイかな？
Matching monogrammed teacups.
イニシャルの入ったペアのティーカップ
You really went all out, huh?
朝から豪勢だなあ
きみの料理は本当に最高だよ！
Your cooking's always the best.
It's been four days since the
secretaries came to check up on me.
秘書２人が橋の下へ訪ねてきてから４日
ふ… あ そういえば きみはいつまで…
By the way, how long are you—
Oh, Master Ko,
いけません行様
ほっぺにご飯粒がついておりますぞ
you've got a bit of rice on your cheek.
あっは… すまない高井
Thanks, Takai.
ちゅる いいえ お礼など…
No need for thanks.
Takai's the only one left at my place.
高井だけが俺の家に居座り続けていた
I didn't think they were all that close.
しかし 一緒に住むほどに
仲がいいとはなあ
Sorry, Nino. There's definitely
something going on there.
いやあニノ…
ありゃあ それどころじゃねえよ
あれは友達以上の
ホモダチってやつだと思うな！
They're probably fudge buddies by now.
Fudge buddies? That sounds nice.
ホモ？ まろやかな響きだな
I know, right? Hey, Nino, we should start
calling Rec "Fudgie" from now on!
そう！ あ そうだニノ
リクのこと ホ○って呼んでやろうぜ！
おお ヒモに続く新しいあだ名か
Ah, a new nickname to follow Moochyman, huh?
Yo! We're coming in, Rec! AKA—
よおー！ 入るぜー！ リク改めホッ…
What is it? Can you hold on a sec?
何だよ ちょっと待ってろ
うわっ わあ！ わああああー！
いいません…
Cavity checks are apparently
a daily Ichinomiya ritual.
相互虫歯チェックという
市ノ宮家の朝の習慣らしい
Chapter 66: "The First..."
Sweet, no cavities.
よし 虫歯はなし… と
White teeth are the key to success.
エリートは白い歯が命ですからな
ふっ… 虫歯？
Cavities?
You all right?
大丈夫か？
Oh, you're here too, Nino?
ああ ニノさんも いらしてたんですか
Get off me!
Yup, I'm here.
おお いるぞ
Cavity Diary
ふむっ！
Great. Would you like a cavity search, too?
よかったらニノさんも虫歯チェック…
行様 それは社の者達だけの秘密ですから
Master Ko, this is meant to be
kept within the family circle.
Cavity Diary
Oh, I guess.
ああ そう？
Besides, if you two are in an actual relationship,
それに 新野様は行様と恋人同士とのこと
wouldn't you rather have your morning ritual be...
でしたら朝することといえば…
a kiss?
キッスなどが一般的ではないでしょうか
That's fairly standard, wouldn't you agree?
ぐふ… あああ…
Ki—
What are you saying? And in front of Nino, too!
何を急にお前！ ニノさんの前で！
Yeah, Baldy! What's your malfunction?!
そうだ このハゲー！ 何言いやがる！
What? Am I wrong?
なにか おかしなことを言いましたかな？
ああ は… ん… 大体ニノさんは
最近までデートも知らなかったんですよ？
Nino didn't even know what a
date was until just recently!
Date, huh? Sounds pretty intense.
デートって何だ？ 禍々しい響きだな
See? She's already forgotten all about it!
ほらあ… また完全に忘れてるし！
So obviously I could never—
だから俺はともかくニノさんにそんな…
あってたまるかあー！
This is unacceptable!
Just as I suspected.
この高井の読みどおり…
What's—
どうした？
No no, don't worry about it.
いえいえいえ 何でも！
この間はつい取り乱してしまったが
よく見てみれば
I may have slightly overreacted
earlier, but now it's obvious—
これは恋というより おままごと…
They're just playing house.
Master Ko is certainly a genius
in the business world.
行様はビジネス界では超天才だが
恋愛に関しては
中学生レベルにも達していない
新野様に至っては小学生レベルですら…
As for Miss Niino, she's probably
still stuck in elementary school.
They can't possibly advance their relationship. In which case, it's not too late...
これでは発展のしようがないのだ
すなわち今なら…
How unusual!
おかしいですなあ 行様
それは恋人同士とは言いませんよ
Master Ko, you can't possibly
call this a "relationship."
I can still pull them apart!
今なら簡単に縁は切れる！
そ そうだよなあー！
Y-Yeah, he's totally right!
Wha—Hoshi?
なっ 星！
If two people are really in love, they'd
wanna kiss all day, every day, year 'round!
普通 恋人同士っつったら
年がら年中チュッチュしてたいもんなのに
And you say you guys
haven't even kissed once?
キスの１回もしたことねえし
できねえって…
あーやだやだ お前らさあ
はっきり言って愛がねえよ！
Ah jeez, this is no good. You know what I think?
You're not in love!
ふへへへへ… やるなハゲ
分かったぜ てめえの考え
Way to go, Baldy. I got yer drift.
Knowing Master Ko... no matter how much
we prod him, he'll never kiss her!
どんなに たきつけても
行様の性格ではキスなどできない！
その上でカップルだってこと自体
完全に否定してやるんだろ
And with that, you can totally
refute their entire relationship.
I-I can't kiss her in front of other people.
なっ… なんで人前でキスなんか…
But aren't you lovers?
恋人なのに？
As I said... most unusual.
おかしいですなあ
I just don't see how you can
say you're in a relationship—
やはり恋人同士とは とても思…
But we are!
恋人だよ！
Rec.
リク
Nino, not now!
ニノさん あとに！
Hey.
おい
今とても込み入った話をし…
We're in the middle of a serious discu—
What's in a kiss?
キスが何なんだ？ 挨拶だろ 恋人同士の
It's just a greeting between lovers, right?
At the tender age of 21, Rec enjoys his first kiss.
リク 21歳 ファーストキスです
Chapter 67: "Alone"
Hey, Rec. We're good now, right?
おいリク これで いいんじゃないのか？
C'mon, you hungry or something?
おい 急に腹でも減ったのか？
Want a dragonfly?
トンボでいいか？
はああ… はえ…
Master Ko.
行様… 随分と
おかしな顔をなさるようになりましたな
I've never seen that look on your face before.
Really? He always looks like this.
そうか？ 割といつも こんな感じだぞ
Is that so?
そうですか…
It's been 10 years since I
began serving Master Ko.
行様にお仕えしだしたのは
10年前のこと…
Yoko
You must be tired from working so hard.
Please fill this out by tomorrow.
Yoko
During that time, my wife divorced me.
わたくしは妻と離婚
Yoko
You must be tired from working so hard.
Please fill this out by tomorrow.
Please fill this out by tomorrow
You must be tired from working so hard.
by tomorrow
working so hard.
My only focus in life was my work,
and eventually my wife got fed up with it.
仕事しか頭にない あたくしに
妻はとっくに愛想が尽きていたようです
I was battered, twisted,
and splintered, like an old tree.
わたくしは打ちのめされ
枯れ木同然となっておりました
And then—
そんな時
You're lucky, Takai.
ラッキーだな高井
Marriage is a foolish contract.
You're lucky you were able to get out of it.
結婚なんて馬鹿な契約
破棄できて幸運だと言ってるんだ
これからは 自分のためだけに
生きられるぞ
From now on, you can live only for yourself.
Humans are strongest when they're alone.
人間は １人の時が一番強い
As you can imagine, Master Ko was always
alone, whether at home or at school.
お言葉どおり行様は
うちでも学校でも いつも１人きりで
He would e-mail me orders during his
breaks throughout the day. It was just...
休み時間に絶えず送られてくる
指示のメールを読むのが
わたくしには とても…
Master Ko.
行様
あっ？ な 何だ？
Yes?
You are weak and flabby!
ヘロヘロのフニャフニャですな！
In other words, you look like a fool.
要約すると馬鹿面です ふふはははは…
Quit laughing! That's not—
はははじゃないよお前！ 何笑って… あ！
ははは… はっ 本当におかしなお顔です
Really, you just look awful.
高井？ 泣いてるぞ？
Takai? You're crying.
Miss Niino.
新野様
If you would,
どうか… いつも なるべく
近くにいて差し上げて下さい
please stand by his side for as long as possible.
We're lovers, right?
恋人だからな
What is this, all of a sudden?
どうしたんだよ 急に
Now then, I'd better get going.
ではわたくしは そろそろ帰ります
へ？ 何？ 帰るの？
Huh? You're leaving?
Master Ko... I had hoped to save
you from your loneliness.
わたくしが 行様を
１人から救って差し上げたいと
I had hoped we could become like father and son.
父子のようになれたらと…
そんなことも思っておりました
But I just can't compete with her motherly love.
母性には勝てませんな
Ah, isn't that...
あ あれは…
That young man seemed quite
fond of Miss Niino himself.
彼は見たところ どうやら新野様を…
Mr. Hoshi, please take care of yoursel—
星様 気をしっか…
I'm a starfish.
僕はヒトデです
僕はヒトデ…
I'm a starfi—
Mr. Hoshi, you have to face reality!
星様！ 現実を
I'm...
僕は ぼ 僕は… 僕はヒトデでえーす！
I-I'm...
I'm... a starfish!
Mr. Hoshi!
星様あー！
うはははあー！ うわあ！ うわあー！
And so, a new species of heart-broken
sea creature has been born.
この日… 心に傷を負った
海洋生物が誕生したのでございます
Chapter 68: "Bluebird"
ピッピピピピ… ピィピピピピ…
It looks like Rec's assistant left.
リクの会社の人間は帰ったらしいな
Uh-huh.
I also heard he didn't look too happy.
何やら元気のない様子だったと
聞いたが…
はーくしゅん！
Ah, that's right... that reminds me.
あ やべ… はずみで思い出しちゃった
Man... this could be bad, huh?
やあ ほんとに参ったなあ
もう ね… ほんと もうね…
I mean, right? You know...
What if it got her pregnant?!
子供ができちゃったら どうしよおおー！
なーんてな！ できねえっつうの！
あっはっはっはっはっ！あーはっは…
Just kidding! It doesn't work that way!
He seems happy, at least.
あいつは元気そうだな
Uh-huh.
Is he on something?
変な物でも食べたのか？
Not sure. He's been like that ever since we kissed.
さあ… この前 私とキスしてから
ずっとああなんだ
A kiss, huh?
キスでか？ あいつも変わったな
Well, he sure has changed.
You think so?
そうか？
So have you.
お前もだ
To be honest, I was very concerned
when you told me you'd taken a lover.
お前が 恋人ができたと言ってきた時は
本当に驚いたぞ
You were?
そうだったか？
I was. To calm myself down,
そうだ 私は気を静めるために…
I put him under 24-hour surveillance
for a full week before we actually met.
リクに会う前に１週間 24時間態勢で
監視して 心の準備をしたもんだ
If he'd acted at all suspicious, I was
ready to "accidentally" pull the trigger.
ちょっとでも不審な行動をしたら
うっかり引き金を引くつもりだったがな
Two between the eyes?
眉間にか？
ふっ　まさか 右足だけだ
No, just a leg wound.
ま お前を傷つけるような男なら
まず村長が名前もやらんだろうからな
But I'm sure if he'd had any intent to harm you,
the Chief would have never given him a name.
Rec may be stubborn, but at least he's sincere.
我が強いが あれで曲がっとらん男だ
And now I get to see you smile all the time.
おかげで… お前が笑うのも見れた
Anyway,
それにしても あいつが あんなに
はしゃいでるのは初めて見るなあ
I've never seen him acting this excited before.
Bluebird! Bluebird!
今は ほっといてやるか…
We should let him enjoy it.
Sure.
うっふふふ あー今なら飛べそーう
I feel like I could fly!
Like I could be a bird!
鳥になれそーう！ ブルーバアアード！
Bluebirrrrrd!
うん 鳥だった
Yup. A bird, for sure.
Indeed. For about two seconds.
ああ ２秒ほど鳥だったな
うわあああ！ 流れが早いい！
助けてえええー！
The current's too strong!
HEEEELLP!!!
惜しかったぞリク
羽ばたきが足りなかったんじゃないか？
You're almost there, Rec!
Try flapping your arms more!
A beak might help, too.
くちばしとか
Your advice is not helping!
そんなアドバイスいりませええー…！
スライド報告は以上… 盗聴は続行中です
That's it for my presentation. We will
continue with the covert observations.
Good work, Shimazaki.
ご苦労だった 島崎
How often did I tell him?
Never be indebted to anyone.
借りを作るな 人を信じるなと
どれだけ言ったか…
If he wants to ruin his own
life, that's fine with me.
あれが どれだけ堕落しようと
知ったことではない…
が 私の代の市ノ宮の姓に
泥を塗らせるわけには いかないな
But I cannot allow him to disgrace
the Ichinomiya family name!
I agree, sir.
仰るとおりかと
By the way, what happened to that
other secretary? Takai, was it?
そういえば島崎 高井とかいう
もう１人の秘書はどうした
I have a separate presentation for him.
資料を用意してあります
そうか
Do you, now? I've heard
he's quite a capable man.
使える男と聞いているが…
Please see for yourself.
ご覧下さい 高井です
This is Takai.
He's been acting this way for some time now.
最近はずっと
こういった感じにございます
島崎
Shimazaki.
His work hasn't suffered, but this is
how he's been spending his free—
一応 仕事はしておりますが
基本的には こうして１人…
島崎！
Shimazaki!
はい
Yes.
You need not show me any
pictures of this man. Ever again.
今後 彼に関しては
画像は用意しなくていい
He's still a father, after all.
パパも人の親です
Chapter 69: Arakawa Qwik-Skit Challenge
What is that?
A pickled radish?
It's gotta be rotten by now.
I'm a starfish!
あの日夕暮れ
Star—
Starfish!
Sorry
It's finally finished!
Wow, nice digs!
No, it's a boiler.
Perfect for burning coal to make white powder anytime!
愛のカケラ 探すたびに
Um, I've been wondering...
Is your house—
I'm wearing it. See?
Next time, on 9 BRIDGE!
いつも何故か 寂しくなる
I knew it!
Illustration:   Renjuro Kindaichi
もう行かなくちゃ
この空泣き出す前に
サカサマになって
君の事探して
いつまでも僕らは
たどり着けないまま
橋の下に立って
流れる渦に在って
いつまでも僕らは
その答え探して
何だろ…
たくあんかな
絶対腐ってるよね
僕はヒトデですううー！
ヒトッ… ヒトデですううー！ ううっ あ
ついに完成だ！
立派な家ですねえ
違うよ これは石灰窯
いつでも白い粉が作れるドリームドームだ
あの前から気になってたんですが
シロさんの家って…
着てるよ ほらこれ
次回 「９ BRIDGE」
やっぱりいー！